[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "How are you going to avoid being chopped out the boat?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "VBN", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "Well, of course, it's a little funny to watch a senator or a congressman who got himself elected by promising the citizen of his state that he would go to Washington to reform government, not raises taxes to pay for our problems.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Why do you care?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "I'm in favor of not raising taxes on all the American people, and as you know the American people quite rightly understand that politicians who say, I'm going to tax the rich, have not finished the sentence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Now what if we had carried -- what if we had carried along the Bush rate of growth of the eight years before Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", ":", "WP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "Well, there were three periods of growth or low growth during the Bush years.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush", "Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grover Norquist"]}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 168, "question": "I'm doing great, Piers, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 169, "answer": "Very interesting this debate now in the Republican Party, especially involving Grover Norquist.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grover"]}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "VBP", "CC", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "JJR", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 172, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 173, "answer": "Well, I think what you heard Grover say and what others have said is that we do need more revenues.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 193, "question": "What's the ideological difference if in the end wealthier people in America are all paying a little bit more tax?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 194, "answer": "Well, it's not really an ideological difference.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "It's all about raising revenue through taxing the wealthier Americans a little bit more, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NNPS", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Chris Christie", "Sandy"]}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "CD", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "Well, I think Chris Christie did job number one when Sandy came through as governor.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Who would you most fear coming up against whoever the Democrat candidate will be in 2016?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "RBS", "JJ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "I'm not fearing anybody.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2016"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "How do you feel about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Well, I don't think about that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "You don't look in the mirror some mornings and think, I'm an icon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "VBG", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Do you ever get anyone have a go at you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "There's the old saying, of all the people who don't like me, just think of the millions who have never heard of me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "When you finished the book, what did you think of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Actually it was really an easy book to write.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 334, "question": "What do you -- what do you make of what's happened to you in those 80 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 335, "answer": "Well, it's kind of -- you can't think about all of that at once.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 339, "question": "Are you a happy guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 340, "answer": "I'm very happy right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "As happy as you've ever been?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Did you ever meet him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Yes, I did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Did you go drinking together?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "We had a drink together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Jack Daniels?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I didn't check the labels.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack Daniels"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 363, "question": "Did I say that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 364, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 372, "question": "Did you make up this morning and have a quick you know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 373, "answer": "I probably did, I probably did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJR", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "Do you take a lot of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "I think some people have more tolerance, you know, for smoking pot than others, and I know people who can take one hit and just go to sleep completely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "CC", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Now what do you make of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "I think it's progress, and I think it's, you know, a great step forward and people are finally growing up and looking around the room and checking things out.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 396, "question": "Are you planning a vacation there soon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "EX", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 397, "answer": "Maybe they'll have a coffee house.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "You can have the Willie Nelson coffee chain, couldn't you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "Why not.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Willie Nelson"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dolly Parton"]}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 418, "question": "If you were consigned to a desert island and you could only listen to one song endlessly on a permanent replay, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "CD", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 419, "answer": "That would be really hard to say, because, you know, this is -- I just recorded a song with with Dolly Parton that I think is the best song that -- she wrote it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "And I told her, I think this is the best song I've heard in a long time.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Do you really believe that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "I believe that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "That could be a strategy that works?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "I do know it would work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "When you look at the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan, what do you think about America's position in the world, its foreign policy in particular, in the last 12 years or so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, as you probably know I'm completely against war.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iraq", "Afghanistan", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "Do you see any chance of actual peace in the Middle East?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Well, if you believe in the bible, where it says two things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Were you pleased he got re- elected?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "-NONE-", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "Yes, I'm glad he got re-elected.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "I mean, how would you describe yourself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I'm not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "You never voted for anybody?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "Well, I have voted, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Did you -- did you this time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "ELSON: Well, I had all kinds of excuses.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "JJR", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "You didn't feel passionately enough about either candidate?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "I really felt like Obama was going to win, that he didn't really need one more vote that he already had sown up.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 482, "question": "And what do you make of the gun debate in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 483, "answer": "Well, you know, I've partied all my life, and, you know, when I was a young I had a BB gun, I had a rubber gun, I had shotguns and rifles and all those things, and I went deer hunting and bear hunting.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Talented guys your sons?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "Yes, they are.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "One of them is here, he did illustrations for the book?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Very proud of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Are you proud of them?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Very much.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "Do you think you've become a better husband?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, yes, I think age has a lot to do with that, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "What have you learned about marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "Nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "You had a great line about divorce?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Yes, the reason divorces are so expensive is they're worth it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "And yet, although you say that, you also -- always stayed fond of your ex's, am I right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", ":", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "CC", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "You must thought that was important?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "I do think it's important to -- you know, especially if you have children which we do, you know, you should stay friends and -- with your ex-wives.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "So if I was to ask you, how many of all the girls you've loved before we would reach how many would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Well, you said properly in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", ":", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "EX", ",", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 548, "question": "How would you define properly?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Well, I wouldn't -- what I said, I wouldn't have put it in there, but --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 556, "question": "How many times have you been in love in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 557, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Is she the -- is she the real love of your life, would you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", ":", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "Well, for the moment she is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Do I ever sing songs to her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 587, "question": "Are you a romantic at heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 588, "answer": "Hundred percent, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 591, "question": "The greatest moment of my life that doesn't involve children or women?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 592, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "If I could let you relive a moment, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "That's a difficult one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "What's the a great life for you personally, for whatever reason?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "Every time I go do a show, where I show up and they show up, and they come and clap and pay good money to hear -- you know, hear me sing songs, it doesn't get any better than that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 602, "question": "You know?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 603, "answer": "Willie, I could talk to you all day.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "Do you like being, for what you were, the most evil man on television?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Well, you know, I don't think I was an evil man, I was just like a Texas businessman, that's all.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "Isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Especially with his own family.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121126pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 646, "question": "But did you like the reputation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 647, "answer": "Of course I do, it is wonderful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]